module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Who beat Clay Aiken in the second season of American Idol?', 
    a: 'Ruben Studdard',
    b: 'Kelly Clarkson',
    c: 'David Cook',
    d: 'Carrie Underwood',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'In 1973, Joe Frazier lost his title to who?', 
    a: 'Muhammad Ali',
    b: 'George Foreman',
    c: 'Mike Tyson',
    d: 'Sugar Ray Leonard',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What New Brunswick, NJ college was originally called Queen\'s College?', 
    a: 'Drew University',
    b: 'Columbia University',
    c: 'Seton Hall University',
    d: 'Rutgers',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a measure of the financial effectiveness and efficiency of a project?', 
    a: 'Cost Performance Index',
    b: 'Total Float Index',
    c: 'Asynchronous Communication Index',
    d: 'Critical Path Analysis',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'When did the Titanic sink?', 
    a: 'Apr 14 1912',
    b: 'Mar 3 1989',
    c: 'Dec 7 1914',
    d: 'Dec 12 1922',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a "blunderbuss"?', 
    a: 'A Gun',
    b: 'A Stupid Person',
    c: 'A Boastful Person',
    d: 'A Plant',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What TV show did Fran Drescher star in?', 
    a: 'Grace Under Fire',
    b: 'The Nanny',
    c: 'Will & Grace',
    d: 'Cheers',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the Philadelphia Flyers mascot?', 
    a: 'Stormy',
    b: 'Wild Wing',
    c: 'Youppi',
    d: 'Gritty',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What protein rich food is coagulated from an extract of soybeans?', 
    a: 'Tofu',
    b: 'Seitan',
    c: 'Soylent Green',
    d: 'Gluten',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was the main star in the TV show Malcolm in the Middle?', 
    a: 'Topher Grace',
    b: 'Christopher Masterson',
    c: 'Haley Joel Osment',
    d: 'Frankie Muniz',
    answer: 'd'
  },
];